我们回到了避难所
we're back out here on the refuge
除了我们的跟踪摄像头
and in addition to our trail cams
我们还安装了一些传感器
we've also installed some sensors
报告我们野生动物的gps位置
to report the gps locations of our wild things
并获取 gps 坐标
and to get the gps coordinates
我们需要向另一个人发送更多请求
we're going to need to send more requests to another
api 现在在最后一节
api now in the last section
我们在 api 中发送请求并最终创建了很多
we send a request in api and ended up creating a lot
重复的
of duplication
如果我们发送更多请求
if we send more requests
我们可能会得到更多的重复
we're probably going to end up with more duplication
所以我们将创建一个抽象来整理并制作
so we'll create an abstraction to tidy that up and make
我们所有的任务都更容易
all of our tasks easier
回到工作室
back here in the studio
我们看到要获得快照，我们必须做两个
we see that to get a snapshot we have to do two
函数的产生
spawn of function
将结果发送回父级
that sends the result back to the parent
并等待
and wait for
并将结果返回给父进程
and return the result to the parent process
所以我们有相当多的重复来获得这些
so we've got a fair amount of duplication to get these
三个不同的快照
three different snapshots
但是看这段代码
but looking at this code
唯一不同的东西
the only thing that varies between one and the other
只是这个获取快照函数的参数
is just the argument to this get snapshot function
这是相机名称
which is the camera name
所以让我们封装这两个东西
so let's encapsulate these two things
在函数中
in functions
我们会将它们放在一个名为 fetcher 的新模块中
and we'll put them in a new module named fetcher
所以我们会把它放在 lib 调查中
so we'll put it in the lib survey
创建一个新文件
create a new file
获取你的 dx
fetch your dx
然后我们需要从处理程序上吊起一些外套，所以
then we need to hoist some coat over from handler so
我们需要这些
we need these
两行我们得到父母和一个产卵
two lines where we get the parent and a spawn
所以我会把它们贴在这里
so I'll paste those in here
回到这里，我们还需要一个接收块
come back over here and we also need a receive block
然后我们将这段代码分成两个函数
then we'll partition this code into two functions
因为我们在做这两件事
since we do these two things at
不同时期
different times
我们将把第一部分放在一个函数中
we're going to put this first part in a function
称为异步
called async
因为它将异步运行一个函数
since it's going to run a function asynchronously
所以这是一个同步
so it's a sync
我们将传入相机名称
and we're going to pass in the camera name
然后我们在哪里引用这台相机
and then where we reference this camera
我们需要在那里传递相机名称
we need to pass in camera name there
我们还需要将其更改为调查
we also need to change this to survey
com 因为我们在这个文件中没有那个别名
com because we don't have that aliased in this file
我会删除这条评论
and I'll remove this comment
因为父母可能是
because the parent could be
任何过程，而不仅仅是请求处理过程
any process not just the request handling process
然后我们将这个接收块
and then we'll put this receive block
在名为 get result 的函数中
in a function named get result
我可以删除这个作业
and I can remove this assignment
因为我只想回来
because I just want to return
接收的返回值
the return value of receive
所以这会阻止
so this will block
如果邮箱中没有匹配的邮件
if a matching message isn't in the mailbox
否则会立即返回文件名
otherwise it will return the file name immediately
所以在调用接收器之后，我们可以做任何我们想做的事情
so after calling a sink we can do whatever we want
然后在稍后的某个时间
and then at some later time
我们可以通过调用 get result 来得到结果
we can get the result by calling get result
那有什么好
so what's nice
关于这个 fetcher 抽象是一个人
about this fetcher abstraction is that a person
使用它不需要知道
using it doesn't need to know
这些消息的结构
the structure of these messages
例如我们使用这个元组的结果
for example we used this tuple with a result
一开始
at the beginning
然后是表达式的结果
and then the result of the expression
然后我们在这里匹配
and then we matched it down here
但因为这些只是这个文件内的地图
but because those are only maps inside of this file
使用这个模块的人
the person that's using this module
不需要知道这些消息的结构
doesn't need to know how these messages are structured
根本
at all
所以我们会把它保存起来，然后再回来处理
so we'll save that away then back over and handler
在最顶部，我们将把它命名为
at the very top we're going to alias this in
然后在我们的路线上
and then down in our route
我们想继续使用它
we want to go ahead and use that
所以我们可以摆脱这个
so we can get rid of this
因为那是在那个 acing 功能中
because that's in that acing function
我们想要改变
and we want to change
所有这些都可以使用该功能
all of these to use that acing function
以同样的方式我们想要改变所有这些
in the same way we want to change all of these
调用我们的获取结果函数
to call our get result function
而不是在这里有一个接收块
instead of having a receive block right here
然后我们会把它保存起来
then we'll save that away
然后通过前任我们将启动我们的服务器
then over an ex we'll fire up our server
我们不需要在单独的进程中运行它
and we don't need to run it in a separate process this
时间
time
然后如果我们转到一个新的终端会话
and then if we go over to a new terminal session
好吧，它应该像以前一样工作
well it should work just as before
我们所做的只是移动一些代码
all we've done is move some code around
果然
and sure enough
我们在一秒钟内得到所有结果
we get back all the results in one second
就像从前一样
just like before
让我们更进一步
let's take it a step further
现在 fetcher 模块可以
right now the fetcher module can
仅用于获取视频摄像头快照
only be used to get a video cam snapshot
因为这就是 spawn 函数的作用
because that's what the spawn function does
但你可能可以
but you can probably
看看我们如何安排事情以便我们可以产卵
see how we can arrange things so that we can spawn
任何功能是的
any function yeah to do that
而不是调用这个特定的函数
instead of calling this specific function
在这里我们希望能够调用任何函数
here we want to be able to call any function
我们要做的是
what we're going to do is
我们要
we're going to
传入函数而不是相机名称
pass in the function instead of the camera name
所以我要把这个乐趣命名为
so I'm going to name this fun that's going to be the
传入的函数
function that gets passed in
而不是在这里运行这个函数
and instead of running this function here
我们将在函数中运行过去，我们可以做到这一点
we'll just run the past in function we can do that fun
就这样
just like that
所以无论这个函数返回什么
so whatever this function returns
将成为信息的一部分
is going to be part of the message
接着
and then
因为消息不是特定于文件名
because the message isn't specific to file names
我只是将这里的变量更改为值
I'm just going to change this variable here to value
现在它可以在不这样做的情况下工作
now it'll work without doing this
但这只是让它看起来更普通
but it just makes it more generic to see hey
函数返回值
the function returns to value
并且该值是消息的一部分
and that value is part of the message
现在名称获取器不再起作用了
now the name fetcher doesn't really work anymore
但请和我们一起去这里一分钟
but just go with us here for a minute
然后回来处理
then back over and handler
我们需要改变这个 acing 函数的调用方式
we need to change how this acing function is called
确保传递给它一个函数
making sure to pass it a function
就这样
just like that
所以现在它更通用了，我们可以传入任何函数
so now it's more generic we can pass in any function
如果我们把它保存起来
if we save that away
去重启我们的服务器
go restart our server
只需在此处进行快速健全性检查
just run a quick sanity check here
很酷，也很有效
cool that works too
现在让我们假设我们要发送一个请求到
now let's suppose we want to send a request to
另一个 api 让我们创建一个名为 tracker ex 的新文件
another api let's create a new file called tracker ex
然后我们将粘贴一些代码
and then we're going to paste in some code
tracker 模块模拟发送请求
the tracker module simulates sending a request
到外部 api
to an external api
获取野生动物的 GPS 坐标
to get the gps coordinates of a wild thing
这是一些了不起的技术
it's some amazing technology
而且看起来很多
and it looks a lot
就像您之前看到的视频摄像头模块
like the video cam module that you saw earlier
这里我们称之为获取位置
here we call get location
为了一件狂野的事情，然后回来
for a wild thing and get back
它的 gps 坐标作为长生不老药地图
its gps coordinates as an elixir map
所以我们
so we
想从我们的路线中调用这个获取位置功能
want to call this get location function from our route
所以回到处理程序
so back over in handler
让我们继续将这条路线从快照重命名为
let's go ahead and rename this route from snapshots to
传感器，因为现在我们正在获取多个传感器
sensors since now we're acquiring multiple sensors
并异步获取大脚怪的位置
and to get the location of bigfoot asynchronously
我们可以使用 fetcher，因为它可以采用任何功能
we can use fetcher since it can take any function
所以就在这里，我们将调用 fetcher
so right down here we'll call fetcher
水槽
a sink
有一个功能
with a function
在这种情况下，它将是一个调查跟踪器
in this case it's going to be a survey tracker
我没有这个别名
I don't have this aliased in
所以我必须在那里使用调查
so I've got to use survey there
获取我将在大脚怪中经过的位置
get location I'm going to pass in bigfoot
然后我们将通过调用获取位置
and then we'll get the location by calling
得到结果，因为它也是通用的
get result since it's also generic
所以我要这样称呼
so I'm going to call this
大脚在哪里
where is bigfoot
获取你的点得到结果
fetch your dot get result
现在我们想将其包含在我们的响应正文中
now we want to include this in our response body
所以在这里我只是要去检查
so down here I'm just going to inspect
我们有快照
we've got snapshots right there
我实际上要把它放在一个两极
I'm actually going to put it in a two pole
所以第一个元素将是我们的快照
so the first element is going to be our snapshots
第二个元素是大脚怪在哪里
and the second element is going to be where is bigfoot
现在如果我们重新启动我们的服务器
now if we restart our server
然后这次发送传感器请求
and then send a request this time for sensors
嗯，那里出了点问题
hmm something went awry there
我们按预期返回一个元组
we get back a tuple as we would expect
第一个元素应该是
and the first element is supposed to be a
我们的快照图像列表
list of our snapshot images
所以那里有清单
so there's the list right there
第二个元素应该是
and the second element is supposed to be
地图 GPS 坐标的线性地图
a map a linear map of the gps coordinates
但坐标实际上最终出现在快照中
but the coordinates actually ended up in the snapshot
列出我们的坐标应该在哪里
list and where our coordinates were supposed to be
我们有一张快照图像
we have a snapshot image
所以出了什么问题
so what went wrong
好吧，如果我们回顾一下代码
well if we look back at the code
我们产生了四个进程
we spawned four processes
每个都发送了一条消息
each of which sent a message
回到父进程的邮箱
back to the parent process's mailbox
但他们回来了
but they came back in a
与我们预期不同的顺序
different order than we expected
为什么即使我们产生了轨道或最后
why well even though we spawned the track or last
它的反应是最快的
its response came back the fastest
对，如果我们在 tracker 中查看它的代码
right if we look at its code over here in tracker
好吧
well it
只睡五百毫秒
only sleeps for five hundred milliseconds
半秒
half a second
所以这是到达邮箱的第一条消息
so it was the first message to arrive in the mailbox
因此回到这里第一次调用以获得结果
therefore back over here this first call to get result
返回位置
returns the location
不是快照，所以这不会是快照
not the snapshot so this isn't going to be a snapshot
并记住我们的获取结果函数是如何实现的
and remember how our get result function is implemented
接收将匹配任何消息
the receive is going to match any message
用这种模式
with this pattern
并且所有进程都由接收器产生
and all process is spawned by a sink
使用该模式发送消息
send a message with that pattern
所以调用获取结果
so calling get result
只会收到邮箱中的下一条消息
will simply receive the next message in the mailbox
或等待消息
or wait for a message
如果还没有到
if one hasn't already arrived
一个技巧是首先获取 gps 位置结果
a hack would be to get the gps location results first
但这正是它只是一个黑客
but that's exactly what it is just a hack
因为进程同时运行
because processes run concurrently
无法保证其中的顺序
there's no guarantee of the order in which
消息被发送
the messages are sent
谁知道可能需要多长时间
who knows how long it might take to
实际定位大脚
actually locate bigfoot
是的，我们需要一些方法来联系电话以获得结果
yeah we need some way to tie the call to get result
到产生该结果的生成过程
to the spawn process that produce that result
所以这个结果应该来自这个产卵过程
so this result should come from this spawn process
我们称之为 get location for bigfoot
the one where we call get location for bigfoot
当我们在这里调用获取结果时，我们想要快照一个
when we call get result here we want snapshot one
好吧，这就是这个 spawn 函数
well that's this spawn function
快照二是这个债券功能
snapshot two is this bond function
你猜对了
and you guessed it
快照三是生成功能
snapshot three is that spawn function
如果我们能把它们绑在一起
if we can tie those together
那么我们调用的顺序无关紧要
then it won't matter the order in which we call
得到结果它总会得到结果
get result it will always get the result
对于产生它的过程
for the process that spawned it
要做到这一点
to do that
我们需要唯一地识别一个过程，我们
we need to uniquely identify a process and we
实际上知道该怎么做
actually know how to do that
它是由它的 pid
it's by its pid
是的，当我们在这里调用水槽时
yeah when we call a sink here
记得看看那个的实现
remember looking at the implementation of that
此 acing 函数中的最后一个调用是生成
the last call in this acing function is to spawn
我们知道产卵
and we know that spawn
总是返回 pid
always returns the pid
所以这里的返回值会给我们一个pid
so the return value back here is going to give us a pid
所以我要签这个给 pid one
so I'm going to sign this to pid one
坑二等
pit two and so on
现在把它们绑在一起
now to tie them together
让我们假设一分钟
let's suppose for a minute
这还行不通
this isn't going to work just yet
但是让我们假设获取结果函数
but let's suppose that the get result function
以 pid 作为参数
takes a pid as the argument
并返回结果
and returns the result
对于那个过程，我们会说好的
for that process we would say okay
对于大脚怪，我们想传入 pid 4
for bigfoot we want to pass in pid four
我们想要它的结果
we want its result
这将是 pid 之一
this would be pid one
坑二
pit two
和三号坑
and pit three
那将是理想的
well that would be ideal
那么订购就无关紧要了
then the ordering wouldn't matter
让我们暂时离开 fetcher 并跳
let's step away from fetcher for a moment and hop
进入性爱看
into sex to see
我们将如何完成这项工作
how we'll make this work
我将不得不放弃它，我回来
I'm going to have to quit it that I get back
提示
to a prompt
所以让我们模拟一下里面发生的事情
so let's sort of simulate what's happening inside
我们的 acing 功能
of our acing function
它做的第一件事是设置父母
the first thing it does is set up the parent
它只是把它分配给自己
and it just assigns it to self
那是调用进程或父进程
that's the calling process or the parent process
然后就像我们刚刚看到的最后一个
and then as we just saw the last
我们的 acing 函数行称为 spawn
line of our acing function called spawn
并返回一个 pid
and returns a pid
在 spawn 函数内部
inside of the spawn function
它只是发回给父母
it just sends back to the parent
一些信息
some message
现在看起来像这个结果
right now it looks like this result
我就放一张硬涂层的快照
and I'll just put in a hard coated snapshot
所以这就是它目前的工作方式
so that's the way it currently works
但我们要做的是包括
but what we'll do is include
生成的进程是 pied
the spawned process is pied
在它发回给父母的消息中
in the message that it sends back to the parent
所以元组目前有
so the tuple currently has
两个元素导致图像
two elements result in the image
我们想在这个前面放一个新元素
we want to put a new element on the front of this
我们可以把它放在任何地方
we could put it anywhere
但我们要选择它的前面
but we're going to choose the front of it
它将成为这个生成过程的 pid
and it's going to be the pid of this spawn process
那么我们如何获得生成过程的pid
well how do we get the pid of the spawn process
好吧，我们称自己
well we call self
它总是返回当前进程的pid
it always returns the pid of the current process
所以当 spawn 在这种情况下被称为 self
and so when spawn is called self in this context
将成为该进程的 pid
is going to be the pid of that process
这将与一号坑相同
which is going to be the same thing as pit one
但我们将其包含在消息中
but we're including it in the message
这样我们就可以拿起它
so that we can pick it up on
事物的接收方
the received side of things
所以在这种情况下，我会发送一个快照
so in this case I'll send a snapshot
然后我要发送第二条消息
then I'm going to send a second message
这次不是发送字符串
this time instead of sending a string
我要使用
I'm going to use
一个长生不老药垫，我们把坐标放在那里
an elixir mat where we put our coordinates in there
我只会用 x 一个
I'm just going to use x one
y 是二
y is two
没关系
doesn't really matter
我们只想要不同于快照名称的东西
we just want something different than a snapshot name
我需要把这个 pid 改成 pid 2
and I need to change this pid over to pid two
然后是第三条消息
and then for the third message
我要发送另一个快照
I'm going to send another snapshot
我们将把这张快照称为一张
we'll just call this one snapshot one
所以它是不同的，这将是 pid 3
so that it's different and this will be pid three
好的，现在让我们看看邮箱内部
okay now let's peek inside of the mailbox
那是家长的邮箱信息
that's the parent's mailbox messages
好的，很酷，我们在这里收到了三条消息
okay cool we've got three messages inside of here
你注意到每个消息元组
and you notice that each of the message tuples
有一个 pid 作为第一个元素
has a pid as the first element
所以快照三是一五十八
so snapshot three was one fifty eight
那是对的 一点五十八
and that's right one fifty eight there
我们的坐标是一六十一
our coordinates were one sixty one that matches up
一六十三是我们最后的快照
and one sixty three is our final snapshot
所以正如我所说，在这里调用自我
so as I said calling self inside of here
将与此处返回的 pid 相同
is going to be the same pid that gets returned here
我们看到了
and we see that
所以现在假设我们想要接收消息
so now suppose we want to receive the message
与 gps 坐标
with the gps coordinates
我们收到的
what we do receive
然后我们要匹配的模式是
and then the pattern we want to match is
一个pid
a pid
然后是原子结果，然后是我们的坐标
and then the atom result and then our coordinates
我就叫绳子
which I'll just call cords
当匹配时
when that matches
我们只想返回坐标
we just want to return the coordinates
但问题是我们要匹配什么 pid
but the question is what pid do we want to match
好吧，坐标在这里
well the coordinates are here
一六十一，这是pid号2
one sixty one and that's pid number two
一六十一
one sixty one
所以这应该是pid 2
so this should be pid two
但没那么快
but not so fast
这是一个变量
this is a variable
我们不想绑定那个变量
and we don't want to bind that variable
到消息中的值
to the value that's in the message
这将是这个 pid
which would be this pid
相反，我们想要一个模式匹配
instead we want a pattern match
pid 也存在的值
pid too's existing value
这是这里的pid结构
which is this pid structure right here
所以要做到这一点，我们需要使用 pin 运算符
so to do that we need to use the pin operator
就是那个胡萝卜
that's that carrot right there
那将是
and that's going to
匹配变量现有值
match against the variables existing value
不将其绑定到新值
not bind it to a new value
所以这是说这个
so this is saying that this
必须与 pid 2 的确切值匹配
must match the exact value of pid two
如果我们这样做
and if we do that
井接收器打开匹配的消息
well receiver turns the matching message
即使它不是邮箱中的第一条消息
even though it's not the first message in the mailbox
这实际上是邮箱中的第二条消息
it was actually the second message in the mailbox
这是正确的，如果第一个
that's right if the first
消息不匹配
message doesn't match
它继续检查剩余的消息
it continues examining the remaining messages
直到找到匹配
until it finds a match
如果它根本找不到匹配项
and if it doesn't find a match at all
它等待新消息到达
it waits for a new message to arrive
现在回到处理程序
now back in handler
我们需要做一些改变才能完成这项工作
we need to make a couple changes to make this work
记得我说过在获取结果中传递一个 pid
remember I said passing a pid in the get result
还不行
won't work yet
所以让我们继续进行更改
so let's go ahead and make the changes
这样就可以了
so that will work
所以在 fetcher
so over in fetcher
当我们发送这个时我们需要做的第一件事
the first thing we need to do when we're sending this
回消息是包括
message back is include the
生成进程是 pid
spawn process is pid
就像我们在 ex 中所做的一样
just like we did in ex
这将是自我在这里
it's going to be self right here
那么我们的gib结果函数需要取pid
then our gib result function needs to take the pid
接着
and then
使用该 pin 运算符对其进行模式匹配
pattern match against it using that pin operator
所以会发生什么
so what happens is
我们调用 self 来获取生成过程
we call self to get the spawn process as
坑并粘贴在消息中
pit and stick it in the message
那将是一样的
that's going to be the same
值作为 spawn 返回的 pid
value as the pid returned by spawn
这是同步的返回值
which is the return value of sync
因此，当处理程序调用同步时，它会返回那个坑
so when handler calls a sync it gets that pit back
然后它在调用 get result 时使用那个坑
then it uses that pit when it calls get result
所以在这种情况下得到结果坑一
so in this case get result pit one
被传入
that gets passed in
然后我们对它进行模式匹配
and then we pattern match against it
所以这只会接收由
so this will only receive messages that were sent by
这个绑定过程
this bond process
现在我们需要确保把它保存起来
now we need to make sure to save this away
还需要保存处理程序
also need to save away the handler
因为它目前没有保存
because it's currently not saved
我们已经准备好再次启动我们的服务器了
and we're ready to fire up our server one more time
确保我们有一张白纸
to make sure we have a clean slate
我杀死了一切，然后我会再次启动 ix
I killed everything and then I'll fire up ix again
然后重启我们的服务器
and then restart our server
现在如果我们发送传感器请求
now if we send a request for sensors
一切都井井有条
well everything's in the right order
我们在第一个列表中有我们所有的快照
we have all of our snapshots in that first list
我们有我们的gps坐标作为第二个
and we have our gps coordinates as the second
该元组的元素
element of that tuple
所以修复了它
so that fixed it
现在在快照的情况下，我们有三个
now in the case of snapshots we have three
调用接收器
calls to a sink
和三个电话以获得结果
and three calls to get result
原来有
it turns out there's
使用管道更简洁的方法
a more concise way to do this using a pipeline
是的，让我们在这里重新安排一些东西来设置它
yeah let's rearrange things a bit here to set that up
我们想把这些放在一个列表中
we want to put these inside of a list
所以让我们摆脱 p
so let's get rid of the p
这将是一个列表
and this will be a list
我需要在这里加一个逗号，在这里加一个逗号
I need to put a comma here and a comma here
就这样
just like that
所以这要做的是产生三个函数
so what this is going to do is spawn three functions
每个相机一个
one for each camera
我们最终会得到一个包含三个坑的列表
and we're going to end up with a list of three pits
现在我们可以做的是获取 pid 列表
now what we can do is take that list of pids
并将其通过管道传输到鸸鹋地图
and pipe it into emu map
对于每一个我们想称之为 fetcher 的孩子
and for every one of those kids we want to call fetcher
得到结果我们知道怎么做
get result we know how to do that
我们可以使用捕获操作符来做到这一点
we can use the capture operator to do that
它只是取回器
it's just going to be fetcher
得到结果
get result
然后我们可以使用
and then we can either use
像这样的和号
ampersand one like that
或者正如我们之前所学
or as we learned earlier
有一条捷径，我们可以用现实的捷径
there's a shortcut we can just use the reality one
所以对于这个列表中的每个坑，它都会调用
so for every pit in this list it's going to call
用那个 pid 得到结果
get result with that pid
当所有过程完成时
and when all the process is finished
虽然我们已经收集
while we've collected
三个文件放大器的列表
a list of three file amps fact
我们将继续并将其分配给快照
we'll just go ahead and assign that to snapshots
然后我们可以在这里摆脱它
and then we can get rid of that down here
并摆脱所有得到的结果
and get rid of all the get results
所以这会起作用
so this will work
但你注意到我们只是在打电话
but you notice we're just calling
在这里获取快照 3 次
get snapshot three times here
每次都以不同的参数传递它
passing it in a different argument each time
所以我们可以进一步细化这个
so we can further refine this
我们要做的是创建一个相机名称列表，所以
what we'll do is create a list of camera names so
凸轮一
cam one
凸轮二和凸轮三
cam two and cam three
然后而不是调用这三次
and then instead of calling this three times
我们要做的是将该列表通过管道传输到新地图中
what we want to do is pipe that list into a new map
对于我们想要调用的每一个相机名称
and for every one of those camera names we want to call
这个 fetcher acing 函数
this fetcher acing function
将它传递给函数调用获取快照
passing it the function calls get snapshot
然后在这里代替凸轮三
and then instead of cam three right here
而我们只想通过
while we just want to pass in
此列表中的下一个摄像机名称
the next camera name from this list
然后我们通过管道将其传递给 get result
and then we pipe that into get result
调用得到结果
which calls get result
对于每一个
for every one of the
此地图返回的列表中的孩子
kids that are in the list returned by this map
让我们继续保存它
let's go ahead and save that away
我们将重新启动我们的服务器
we'll restart our server
给它一个快速的健全性检查
give it a quick sanity check
很酷，仍然有效
and cool that still works
这种方法的一个优点是它
one advantage to this approach is that it
总是调用 git result
always calls git result
对于每个过程
for each process
我们不必记住
we don't have to remember
调用它一定次数
to call it a certain number of times
一个缺点是我们的跟踪器流程就在这里
one disadvantage is our tracker process right here
直到
doesn't get spawn until
收到快照后
after the snapshots have been received
这意味着我们创建了一个不需要的
which means we've created an unwanted
我们代码中的同步点
synchronization point in our code
再次
again
我们必须等待所有这些快照回来
we've got to wait for all these snapshots to come back
在我们去弄清楚大脚怪在哪里之前
before we can then go figure out where bigfoot is
所以在这种情况下，我们想先生成所有东西
so in this case we want to spawn everything first
所以我要把它移到这里
so I'm going to move this up here
我们将生成获取位置去寻找大脚怪
we'll spawn the get location go look for bigfoot
然后我们将继续生成我们的 get
and then we'll go ahead and spawn our get
快照我们将等待快照
snapshots we'll wait for the snapshots
然后他们回来的时候
and then by the time they're back
好吧，我们也应该有一个大脚怪的结果
well we should have a result for bigfoot too
所以我们会得到那个结果
so we'll just get that result
现在产生一个一次性的过程
now spawning a process for a one off
像这样的同步任务
a synchronous task like this
并在以后得到结果
and getting its result at a later time
如此普遍，以至于 elixir 提供了一个抽象
is so common that elixir provides an abstraction
是的，类似于我们的 fetcher 模块
yeah similar to our fetcher module
elixir 有一个任务模块
elixir has a task module
它包括几个便利功能
it includes several convenience functions
其中两个有效地做同样的事情
two of which effectively do the same
作为我们的取物器
thing as our fetcher
并且因为我们按照我们的方式设计了 fetcher
and because we designed fetcher the way we did
眨眼眨眼任务是替代品
wink wink task is a drop in replacement
所以让我们改变我们的路线来使用任务
so let's change our route to use task
我将从这里的大脚开始
and I'll start with bigfoot here
我们只是将此处的 fetcher 模块更改为任务
we just change the fetcher module here to task
和 acing 函数和 fetcher 类似
and similar to the acing function and fetcher
任务具有执行功能
task has an acing function
它产生一个运行函数的进程
it spawns a process that runs a function
然后调用cind发送
then cind is called to send
该函数返回父进程
that functions result back to the parent process
听起来很熟悉
sounds pretty familiar
类似于 fetcher 中的 git result 函数
in similar to the git result function in fetcher
任务模块有一个称为权重的函数
the task module has a function called a weight
在那个函数里面有一个接收块
and inside of that function there's a receive block
匹配并返回
that matches and returns
同步发送的消息
the message sent by sync
现在与 fetcher 不同，我们不会返回 pid
now unlike the fetcher we don't get back a pid
当我们称任务为接收器时
when we call task a sink
我们实际上得到了一个任务结构
we actually get back a task structure
所以我要调用那个任务
so I'm going to call that task
并且被击中的仅包括父进程 pid
and the struck just includes the parent process pid
它称它为所有者，也称其为试用进程 pid
it calls it the owner and also the trial process pid
然后它使用那个任务结构
and then it uses that task structure
匹配生成过程
to match up the spawn process
结果我们必须在这里传递
with the results we have to pass it in here
任务听起来很熟悉
task sounds pretty familiar
然后让我们继续更改我们的管道以使用
then let's go ahead and change our pipeline to use
任务以及这里的任务
task as well so task here
不必改变水槽，但必须改变这个
don't have to change a sink but have to change this
超过一个重量
over to a weight
很酷，所以虽然我们学到了很多写作 fetcher
cool so while we learned a lot writing fetcher
我们实际上不再需要它了
we don't actually need it anymore
当一个计划一起出现时，你不只是喜欢它吗
don't you just love it when a plan comes together
是的，我也喜欢删除这些别名
yeah I do I also love removing these aliases
那是我们必须编写的更少的代码
that's less code that we have to write
所以我会在那里删除它
so I'll just remove that there
把它存起来
save that away
重启我们的服务器
restart our server
最后一次发送请求
send the request one final time
它就像以前一样工作
and it works just like it did before
但现在我们需要维护的代码更少了
but now we have less code to maintain
现在你基本上知道会发生什么了
now you basically know what happens
在任务模块的底层
under the hood of the task module
你会想用
you'll want to use
在需要运行函数的情况下执行任务
task in situations where you need to run a function
异步任务
a task asynchronously
在一个短暂的过程中
in a short lived process
所以在什么其他用例中我们的过程是有用的
so in what other use cases our process is useful
好在下一节
well in the next section
我们将看一个具有
we'll look at an example of a process that has a
更长的使用寿命并响应多条消息
longer life and responds to multiple messages